Finding Aid for Michigan Daily Records, 1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
Michigan Daily records
1950-2006
Bentley Historical Library
Michigan Daily (Organization)
93828 Bimu F3g 2
45 linear feet
18.3 MB (online)
University of Michigan student newspaper. Records include biographical information about University of Michigan faculty, staff, and administrators, including news clippings, news releases, and curriculum vitae; and negatives and contact prints of images of University buildings, student and staff activities, athletic events, and life in Ann Arbor, Michigan; and portraits of faculty, staff, and administrators.
The record group (donor No. 2878 ) has been received in several accessions.
The collection is open for research.
The Michigan Daily is a student newspaper published by the students of the University of Michigan. First published in 1890, the newspaper was called the U of M Daily and the Michigan Daily-News before acquiring its present name in 1903. It is the oldest college newspaper in continuous publication in the United States and was the first college paper west of Cornell to be published daily. The Michigan Daily is staffed by students and is self-funded. Since 1903 it has been under the jurisdiction of the Board for Student Publications (formerly the Board in Control of The Michigan Daily), an agency of the Board of Regents composed of both students and presidential appointees. The Board has full authority over the newspaper's financial and legal affairs and serves in an advisory capacity in other matters. The Michigan Daily has always maintained a great deal of editorial freedom and has won numerous awards. It reports on campus issues and athletics as well as local and national news in five weekly issues during Fall and Winter semesters and one weekly issue in Spring and Summer.
This record group consists primarily of visual materials created by the photographic staff of The Michigan Daily. The photographs cover the full spectrum of activities on campus -- classroom scenes, staff and faculty portraits, academic ceremonies, student protests, athletics, student life, speakers and musical performers, as well as some Ann Arbor scenes and events and occasional events of state and national significance. To date, no administrative records have been donated to the Bentley Historical Library. The records were received in several accessions. The organization of the records in part reflects these multiple accessions with several distinct runs of negatives and prints (though there may be some overlap in years.
Michigan daily.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.); Demonstrations -- Michigan -- Ann Arbor.; Digital file formats.; Photographs.; University of Michigan -- History.; University of Michigan -- Faculty.; University of Michigan -- Biography.; University of Michigan -- Sports.; University of Michigan -- Buildings.; University of Michigan -- Faculty.; University of Michigan -- Football.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Political activity.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Social life and customs -- 1961-1970.; University of Michigan -- Students -- Social life and customs -- 1971-1980.
- Negatives-Chronological, 1963-1980; 4.5 linear feet
  The series Negatives-Topical, ca. 1963-1980, is comprised of 35mm negatives shot by Michigan Daily staff photographers. Each entry in the container list represents an individual envelope containing one or more negative strips. The envelopes were labeled and dated by the photographer and a listing was later compiled by Daily staff. The photographers' envelope labels were sometimes rather cryptic but for the most part have been maintained as transcribed by the Daily staff. In a few cases, obvious errors in transcription have been corrected and abbreviations expanded. Occasionally additional identifying information has been supplied by the processing archivist. Each container list entry includes the envelope title, date and the name of the photographer. Missing, unknown or uncertain information is indicated by a "(?)".
  - 1963-1965
    - DAC Pickets, 1963 (Box 1)
      (Kamalaker Rao)
    - North Campus Park-In, Summer 1964 (Box 1)
    - Movie Protest, "Sex and the Single Girl", Winter 1964 (Box 1)
  - 1966
    - Pratt's Posters, 01/11/1966 (Box 1)
      (Goldstein)
    - Bookstore Protest March, 01/21/1966 (Box 1)
      (Pollock, Jon)
    - APA at Airport, 9/66 (Box 1)
      (Horwitz)
    - Unfinished Apts., 09/01/1966 (Box 1)
      (Hassberger)
    - Kodaly, 09/06/1966 (Box 1)
      (Lowe, Tina)
    - "The Blacks", 09/07/1966 (Box 1)
      (Allen, Mike)
    - Law Club-Grass Signs, 09/07/1966 (Box 1)
      (Horwitz, Mike)
    - Band Practice, 09/14/1966 (Box 1)
    - Rush Sign-up, 09/14/1966 (Box 1)
    - Arjay Miller, 09/15/1966 (Box 1)
    - Vera Baits, 09/21/1966 (Box 1)
      (Josephson)
    - Concert, 09/29/1966 (Box 1)
      (Soberman)
    - Pierpont Sit-In, 09/29/1966 (Box 1)
    - Admin Bldg. Sit-In, 09/30/1966 (Box 1)
      (Junne)
    - MSU-TV Ticket Sales, 09/29/1966 (Box 1)
    - Hill Aud./State Game, 10/08/1966 (Box 1)
      (Sneard, Tom)
    - DVD? Lectures, 10/12/1966 (Box 1)
    - Lenoy? Gift Shop, 10/12/1966 (Box 1)
      (Copi)
    - UAC Football, 10/14/1966 (Box 1)
    - Frietag Lecture, 10/14/1966 (Box 1)
    - Rackham Students w/Haber, Smith, Spurr, 10/18/1966 (Box 1)
      (Sheard)
    - Regents Meeting, 10/21/1966 (Box 1)
    - Homecoming Parade and Queen, 10/21/1966 (Box 1)
    - Homecoming, 10/22/1966 (Box 1)
      (Loughlin)
    - Picket People at County Bldg, 10/15/1966 (Box 1)
      (unknown)
    - Boulding, Weston, Asch, 10/26/1966 (Box 1)
    - Death of God Conference, 10/28/1966 (Box 1)
      (Badamo)
    - Blue Front, 10/29/1966 (Box 1)
    - Blue Front, 10/30/1966 (Box 1)
    - Soph Show, 11/02/1966 (Box 1)
    - SGC, 11/02/1966 (Box 1)
      (Sax)
    - Stadium Under Snow, 11/03/1966 (Box 1)
    - Union Bus Stop, 11/04/1966 (Box 1)
    - Bldg. Soph Show, 11/04/1966 (Box 1)
    - Bunys Eliot & Peter-?, 11/04/1966 (Box 1)
    - Vetzner & Daily Trophy, 11/01/1966 (Box 1)
      (Wing)
    - Daily vs State News, 11/11/1966 (Box 1)
    - Regent Elect Brown and ?, 11/11/1966 (Box 1)
    - Union Mass Meeting, 11/15/1966 (Box 1)
      (Soberman?)
    - "Wedding Band" Luncheon, 11/16/1966 (Box 1)
    - Voting in Front of Union, 11/16/1966 (Box 1)
    - Vote Count SGC, 11/16/1966 (Box 1)
      (Horowitz)
    - Voting in Front of Union, 11/16/1966 (Box 1)
    - Jacobson's Adv., 11/16/1966 (Box 1)
    - Jake's Boutique, 11/19/1966 (Box 1)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan, 11/30/1966 (Box 1)
    - Wasserman, 12/01/1966 (Box 1)
  - 1967
    - January-June
      - Marching, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Michigan Daily Offices?, Summer 1967 (Box 1)
      - Faculty Meeting, 1/67 (Box 1)
      - West Quad Fire, 01/09/1967 (Box 1)
        (Baker)
      - Power Theater, 01/09/1967 (Box 1)
      - Lit School Meeting, 01/10/1967 (Box 1)
      - Apt Sys. Stuff, 01/18/1967 (Box 1)
      - Art Show, 01/23/1967 (Box 1)
      - Spring (?), 01/23/1967 (Box 1)
      - Cinema-Guild Bucket Drive, 01/25/1967 (Box 1)
      - Davis' Art Exhibit, 01/26/1967 (Box 1)
      - Snow, 01/27/1967 (Box 1)
      - Doc Losh/Davis Art Show, 01/27/1967 (Box 1)
      - Snow, 02/03/1967 (Box 1)
      - Halberstam, David, 02/15/1967 (Box 1)
        (Herstein, Richard)
      - State St., Corner, 02/15/1967 (Box 1)
      - Draft Committee, 02/05/1967 (Box 1)
      - City Election Candidates, 02/07/1967 (Box 1)
        (Bockoff)
      - Pres. Commission, 02/08/1967 (Box 1)
      - Dr. Miller News Conf., 02/08/1967 (Box 1)
      - Tice's Mens Shop, 02/09/1967 (Box 1)
      - Ribicoff & Panel, 02/09/1967 (Box 1)
      - Conyers, Rep. J., 02/17/1967 (Box 1)
      - Marcus Plant, 02/18/1967 (Box 1)
      - Artworks, 02/20/1967 (Box 1)
      - Panhell Prexy, 02/20/1967 (Box 1)
      - Art Show, 02/22/1967 (Box 1)
      - George Romney (?), 02/24/1967 (Box 1)
      - NCN Editors, 02/26/1967 (Box 1)
        (Bennett)
      - Sesqui copy negs, 02/21/1967 (Box 1)
      - Miller, Arthur, 02/28/1967 (Box 1)
      - Ed English, 03/01/1967 (Box 1)
      - Musket Ad, 03/09/1967 (Box 1)
      - Ad Bldg, 03/10/1967 (Box 1)
      - SGC Candidates WCBN, 03/14/1967 (Box 1)
        (Bockoff, Chuck)
      - Gilbert & Sullivan Rehearsal, 03/14/1967 (Box 1)
      - Snow Girl, 03/21/1967 (Box 1)
      - City council, 03/22/1967 (Box 1)
      - SGC Waivers, 03/22/1967 (Box 1)
      - Ann Arbor poor, 03/24/1967 (Box 1)
      - Housing, 03/25/1967 (Box 1)
        (Gordon, Stu)
      - Good Humor, 03/28/1967 (Box 1)
      - "Flexible" Bus, 4/67 (Box 1)
      - Lawyer Conference, 04/05/1967 (Box 1)
      - Demonstration, 04/08/1967 (Box 1)
      - Commuter Bus, 04/12/1967 (Box 1)
      - Parking Structure, 04/12/1967 (Box 1)
      - Misc., 5/67 (Box 1)
      - Flick's Bar, 05/31/1967 (Box 1)
        (Thomas Copi)
      - Taft & Esch, 06/04/1967 (Box 1)
        (Forsythe)
      - War Research Panel, 06/05/1967 (Box 1)
        (Kessler)
    - July-December
      - Softball Championships, 08/07/1968 (Box 1)
        (Lee)
      - Grad Rent Strike, 08/08/1967 (Box 1)
        (Copi?)
      - CNP Rally, 08/31/1967 (Box 1)
        (Shef)
      - Student Relations Comm, 9/67 (Box 1)
        (Forsyth)
      - Follett's Bookstore, 09/01/1967 (Box 1)
        (Botkin)
      - Labor Day Mixer, 09/01/1967 (Box 1)
      - Follett's Bookstore, 09/01/1967 (Box 1)
      - Marching Band Practice, 09/02/1967 (Box 1)
        (Sheffield)
      - Detroit Arts Strike, 09/05/1967 (Box 1)
        (Book Steni)
      - Domm Strike, 09/11/1967 (Box 1)
        (Bruckner)
      - Macbird, 09/15/1967 (Box 1)
      - Hatch's Backyard, 09/19/1967 (Box 1)
      - Psych. Bookstore & Poster, 09/19/1967 (Box 1)
      - Faxon, 09/23/1967 (Box 1)
      - Meadow and the Car, 09/25/1967 (Box 1)
      - Shakespeare Garden Exhibit, 09/29/1967 (Box 1)
        (Forsyth, Jim)
      - Samuelson, 10/03/1967 (Box 1)
      - Hatcher's New House & UAC, 10/06/1967 (Box 1)
      - Dailey Libels vs UAC muggers, 10/06/1967 (Box 1)
      - New Lost City Ramblers, 10/06/1967 (Box 1)
      - Vulcan/Angell Hall/Hatcher, 10/07/1967 (Box 1)
      - Romney & Exch Press Conf., 10/07/1967 (Box 1)
      - Peace Mobile, 10/11/1967 (Box 1)
      - Conductron, 10/15/1967 (Box 1)
      - VP Norman, 10/16/1967 (Box 1)
      - Joint Judiciary Council, 10/17/1967 (Box 1)
        (Cassidy)
      - Diag Rally/Regents meeting, 10/18/1967 (Box 1)
        (Wexer)
      - Home Coming Parade, 10/20/1967 (Box 1)
      - James Farmer at Tappan, 10/20/1967 (Box 1)
        (Cass)
      - ROTC Field Day, 10/27/1967 (Box 1)
      - Felheim Lecture, 10/30/1967 (Box 1)
        (Kessler, Anita)
      - Laird, Melvin, 10/30/1967 (Box 1)
      - Halloween Free Art, 10/30/1967 (Box 1)
      - Colchness (?) Free Art, 11/05/1967 (Box 1)
      - Carbon Monoxide in Gen Lib, 11/05/1967 (Box 1)
      - Debate Team, 11/07/1967 (Box 1)
      - AFS, 11/07/1967 (Box 1)
      - North Campus Art Exhibit, 11/07/1967 (Box 1)
      - McCarthy, 11/10/1967 (Box 1)
      - IHA-IFC Football, 11/12/1967 (Box 1)
      - Anthrax and Protesters, 11/13/1967 (Box 1)
      - A&D Darkroom, 11/13/1967 (Box 1)
      - U Events Bldg, 11/15/1967 (Box 1)
      - SGC Meeting, 11/16/1967 (Box 1)
      - Turkey Hunt at Markley, 11/17/1967 (Box 1)
      - Issais Press President, 11/19/1967 (Box 1)
        (Sener)
      - Dr. Felheim, 11/17/1967 (Box 1)
      - Books for Christmas, 11/29/1967 (Box 1)
      - Sequi, 11/29/1967 (Box 1)
      - Sam Friedman, E. Chester, 11/30/1967 (Box 1)
  - 1968
    - January-June
      - 1968 Convention, Undated (Box 1)
      - Union Mixer, 01/05/1968 (Box 1)
      - UGLi Interior, 01/11/1968 (Box 1)
      - AAUP Meeting, 01/14/1968 (Box 1)
      - Kozinski at Rackham, 01/14/1968 (Box 1)
      - Irving Howe, 01/15/1968 (Box 1)
      - Bursley Sit In, 01/16/1968 (Box 1)
      - Roger Craiz Ptgs, 01/22/1968 (Box 1)
      - Radical Caucus, 01/23/1968 (Box 1)
        (Dreyfuss)
      - Chrysler Center Model for Continuing Eng. Educ., 01/24/1967 (Box 1)
      - Koeneke, 01/26/1968 (Box 1)
      - Apts Unlimited Picketers, 01/27/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dionysys Art South Quad, 01/28/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dr. Fantans Puppet Show, 01/29/1968 (Box 1)
      - Maynard Street, 2/68 (Box 1)
      - Prof. Stein UGLI, 2/68 (Box 1)
      - Debate at the Ark (?), 02/01/1968 (Box 1)
      - Salomee, 02/01/1968 (Box 1)
        (Forstyh)
      - City Hall Pickets/Housing, 02/01/1968 (Box 1)
      - Hutcherson, 02/03/1968 (Box 1)
      - Worlds Fair, 02/03/1968 (Box 1)
      - Diag, 02/05/1968 (Box 1)
      - Rickman Playright, 02/13/1968 (Box 1)
      - Paul Bunyan Contest (?), 02/15/1968 (Box 1)
      - Jeny and Satires, 02/15/1968 (Box 1)
        (Sax.)
      - Quartet etc., 02/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - SACUA Meeting, 02/19/1968 (Box 1)
        (Kessler/Forsyth)
      - Rothwax, 02/21/1968 (Box 1)
      - May, Rollo, 02/22/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dow Debate, 02/22/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dance Concert, 02/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - Wild West, 02/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Art/Electronic Pictures, 02/26/1968 (Box 1)
      - ? Terrace, 03/04/1968 (Box 1)
      - City Hall, 03/18/1968 (Box 1)
      - College Quiz Winners, 03/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - 6 Lee Clips (Musical performance at Hill), 03/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dean Hayes, 03/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - Miller (Prof.), 03/26/1968 (Box 1)
      - Con Con (?), 03/28/1968 (Box 1)
      - Demonstration, 04/05/1968 (Box 1)
      - Headlines, 04/06/1968 (Box 1)
      - Armory/Demonstration, 04/08/1968 (Box 1)
      - Handicapped, Undated (Box 1)
      - Okrent & Freshman Frisbee, 04/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Commencement, 5/68 (Box 1)
        (Sacks)
      - Lucy's Stuff, 05/02/1968 (Box 1)
      - Pickets at City Hall, 05/06/1968 (Box 1)
      - Pickets/Dow, 05/07/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dow Pickets, 05/08/1968 (Box 1)
      - Admin. Bldg. Interior, 05/13/1968 (Box 1)
        (?)
      - Janitors, 05/16/1968 (Box 1)
      - Poor Going to D.C., 05/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - Poor Going to D.C., 05/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - Volleyball, 05/22/1968 (Box 1)
      - Admin. Bldg./Destruction, 05/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - Orientation Dir. Interview, 05/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Draft Board Pickets, 06/03/1968 (Box 1)
      - MSU Protest, 06/06/1968 (Box 1)
      - Wheeler, Albert, 06/07/1968 (Box 1)
      - Hatcher Library Reading Room, 06/13/1968 (Box 1)
      - Inst. for Sci. & Tech., 06/13/1968 (Box 1)
      - Green Beret Picket, 06/29/1968 (Box 1)
        (Robins)
      - New Ad Building, 06/27/1968 (Box 1)
    - July-December
      - Concerned Democrats, 07/02/1968 (Box 1)
        (Eric)
      - Yost Locker Rooms, 07/02/1968 (Box 1)
        (Pergeaux)
      - Canham, Don, 07/02/1968 (Box 1)
      - Peace March, 07/09/1968 (Box 1)
      - Hillel/buttons, 07/11/1968 (Box 1)
      - Ed. Meeting, 07/11/1968 (Box 1)
      - Shaving, 07/12/1968 (Box 1)
      - "Mommy" Lucy, 07/12/1968 (Box 1)
      - Soccer "B", 07/16/1968 (Box 1)
      - Gym Clinic, "B", 07/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - Biafran Meeting, 07/23/1968 (Box 1)
        (Robins, Larry)
      - Job Placement, 07/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Orientation B, 07/25/1968 (Box 1)
      - Orientation A, 07/25/1968 (Box 1)
      - MCC In Motown, 07/27/1968 (Box 1)
      - Impounded Car, 07/28/1968 (Box 1)
      - Sussman, 07/30/1968 (Box 1)
      - Construction Near Ad. Bldg., 07/30/1968 (Box 1)
      - Figaro, 07/31/1968 (Box 1)
      - Wines Field Meeting, 08/01/1968 (Box 1)
        (Robbins)
      - Instruments, 08/04/1968 (Box 1)
      - GOP Convention, 08/06/1968 (Box 1)
        (Lehner)
      - Niehuss, 08/06/1968 (Box 1)
      - GOP in Miami, 08/09/1968 (Box 1)
      - GOP in Miami, 08/09/1968 (Box 1)
      - Arab Convention, 08/31/1968 (Box 1)
      - Ron Johnson Broken Thumb, 09/03/1968 (Box 1)
      - Football Scrimmage, 09/07/1968 (Box 1)
      - Tennis Tournament, 09/07/1968 (Box 1)
        (Vaughan)
      - Welfare Rally Diag, 09/09/1968 (Box 1)
      - AD Bldg, 09/10/1968 (Box 1)
      - Freshmen, 09/12/1968 (Box 1)
      - West Quad Space Problem, 09/13/1968 (Box 1)
      - Loken, Newt Going to Mexico, 09/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - Chattens, 09/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - Procol Harum, 09/17/1968 (Box 1)
      - Electrical Workers, 09/19/1968 (Box 1)
        (Morton)
      - Hospital Press Conference, 09/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - Softball, 09/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - IM Athlete of Year, 09/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - Dog, 09/21/1968 (Box 1)
      - Archery, 09/23/1968 (Box 1)
      - String Quartet, 09/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Bars on Wall, 09/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Michigan Speedway, 09/26/1968 (Box 1)
        (Barbass)
      - Western Union, 09/27/1968 (Box 1)
        (Norton)
      - Band Practice, 10/01/1968 (Box 1)
        (Sarah)
      - Band Practice, 10/01/1968 (Box 1)
      - Radical Studies at Newman Ct, 10/02/1968 (Box 1)
      - Students meeting with Fleming, 10/12/1968 (Box 1)
      - Bombed Bldg., 10/14/1968 (Box 1)
      - HUAC Lecture, 10/14/1968 (Box 1)
      - Construction Angell Hall, 10/15/1968 (Box 1)
      - DKE House Burnt, 10/16/1968 (Box 1)
      - Stone, I.F., 10/16/1968 (Box 1)
      - UAC Meeting, 10/15/1968 (Box 1)
      - Church on Huron, 10/18/1968 (Box 1)
      - Wallace/Flint, 10/18/1968 (Box 1)
      - White Rabbit, 10/19/1968 (Box 1)
      - Murray, Madeline, 10/21/1968 (Box 1)
      - Wheeler, Albert, 10/24/1968 (Box 1)
      - Nonnan, Steve, 10/25/1968 (Box 1)
      - Daily Libel, 10/25/1968 (Box 1)
        (Spunda)
      - Daily Libel, 10/25/1968 (Box 1)
      - Minn., 10/26/1968 (Box 1)
      - IM Football, 10/29/1968 (Box 1)
      - Nixon, 10/30/1968 (Box 1)
      - Passports, 11/01/1968 (Box 1)
      - Diag, 11/02/1968 (Box 1)
      - UM/ILL Glee Clubs, 11/09/1968 (Box 1)
      - Illyich, 11/11/1968 (Box 1)
      - SGC election, 11/12/1968 (Box 1)
      - Rasklim, 11/14/1968 (Box 1)
      - Regents Meeting, 11/15/1968 (Box 1)
      - Art Show in Union, 11/19/1968 (Box 1)
      - Johnson, Ron and orange, 11/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - Residential College, 11/20/1968 (Box 1)
      - Pep Rally, 11/21/1968 (Box 1)
      - Hog Farm, 11/21/1968 (Box 1)
      - Junk Yard, 11/22/1968 (Box 1)
        (Dreyfuuss)
      - Jan Phlegar, 12/03/1968 (Box 1)
      - Winter Supplement (Fashion?), 12/04/1968 (Box 1)
      - Neubacker/MUG, 12/06/1968 (Box 1)
  - 1969
    - January-June
      - International Festival, 1/69 (Box 1)
        (Sara K)
      - Tog Shops, 1/69 (Box 1)
      - Cube, 01/08/1969 (Box 1)
        (Krulwich)
      - Registration, 01/08/1969 (Box 1)
        (Sara K?)
      - Jim Kweskin, 01/10/1969 (Box 1)
      - Kaszinsky, Jerry, 01/13/1969 (Box 1)
      - Doc Watson, 01/17/1969 (Box 1)
      - Residential College, 01/18/1969 (Box 1)
      - LSA Meeting, 01/27/1969 (Box 1)
      - Levine, Les, 01/28/1969 (Box 1)
      - Black Poets, 01/29/1969 (Box 1)
      - LSA Sit-In, 01/30/1969 (Box 1)
      - Israel Rally, 2/69 (Box 1)
      - Theater of Cruelty, 2/69 (Box 1)
      - The Believers, 02/01/1969 (Box 1)
        (Sara?)
      - The Wheel, 02/01/1969 (Box 1)
      - Woodchuck, 02/01/1969 (Box 1)
      - Faculty meeting, 02/03/1969 (Box 1)
      - Rowlandsman?, 02/04/1969 (Box 1)
      - Language Lab, 02/05/1969 (Box 1)
      - Montoya, 02/06/1969 (Box 1)
        (Diehl, Jim)
      - Earl Reynolds (Quaker who went to N. Vietnam), 02/10/1969 (Box 1)
      - Harris for Mayor, 02/12/1969 (Box 1)
      - Soc. Undergrad Mtg., 02/12/1969 (Box 1)
      - SGC Mtg., 02/13/1969 (Box 1)
      - Hillel Debate, 02/16/1969 (Box 1)
      - $50, 02/17/1969 (Box 1)
      - Phiep Rush, 02/17/1969 (Box 1)
      - Black Poet, 02/18/1969 (Box 1)
      - Entertainer, 02/19/1969 (Box 1)
      - Arb, 02/22/1969 (Box 1)
        (Peter?)
      - Hirschman's impounded car, 02/22/1969 (Box 1)
      - Curriculum Committee Mtg, 02/24/1969 (Box 1)
      - Rev. Gary Davis, 02/24/1969 (Box 1)
      - Panhellenic (?), 02/24/1969 (Box 1)
      - Senator Packwood, 02/27/1969 (Box 1)
      - Meat Market, 3/69 (Box 2)
        (Jay)
      - Mock Court at Law School, 3/69 (Box 2)
      - Animals, 03/01/1969 (Box 2)
        (Lavely)
      - EMU Protest, 03/01/1969 (Box 2)
      - Harris for Mayor, 03/02/1969 (Box 2)
      - LSA Faculty Meeting (Hayes), 03/03/1969 (Box 2)
      - Community Computer, 03/10/1969 (Box 2)
      - Pizza Bob, 03/12/1969 (Box 2)
      - Rent Strike, 03/12/1969 (Box 2)
      - Diag Rally for Mayor and Garskoff, 03/12/1969 (Box 2)
        (Krulwich, Sara)
      - New Law Club Members, 03/13/1969 (Box 2)
      - Black Student Union Rally Against Daily, 03/18/1969 (Box 2)
      - Iolanthe, 03/18/1969 (Box 2)
      - Professor Leslie White, 03/19/1969 (Box 2)
      - Harris Ugliness Walk, 03/19/1969 (Box 2)
      - Dance Concert, 03/21/1969 (Box 2)
      - LSA Faculty Meeting, 03/24/1969 (Box 2)
      - S.D.S. Navy Recruiter, 03/25/1969 (Box 2)
      - Political Science Teach-in, 03/26/1969 (Box 2)
      - 10 Year Old Radicals, 03/27/1969 (Box 2)
      - Roundhouse Railroad Station, 03/28/1969 (Box 2)
      - Education School Show, 03/28/1969 (Box 2)
      - Globetrotters, 03/31/1969 (Box 2)
      - Black Fashions, 4/69 (Box 2)
      - Lysistrada (Play), 4/69 (Box 2)
      - Drug Forum, 04/01/1969 (Box 2)
      - Welfare at Sears, 04/03/1969 (Box 2)
      - Cube and AP Cube, 04/10/1969 (Box 2)
      - Michigras, 04/12/1969 (Box 2)
      - Reta De Vries, 04/16/1969 (Box 2)
      - Residential College Meet, 04/17/1969 (Box 2)
      - Sandal for AD?, 5/69 (Box 2)
      - Willie Lomax, 05/06/1969 (Box 2)
      - Dow Protest, 05/07/1969 (Box 2)
        (Cass?)
      - Dow Protest, 05/07/1969 (Box 2)
      - A. Ross (V.P.), 05/21/1969 (Box 2)
      - Sun Ra, 05/23/1969 (Box 2)
      - Daily Staff Reading Argus, 05/28/1969 (Box 2)
      - SEI, 06/04/1969 (Box 2)
        (Eisner, Jack)
      - School Board Candidates, 06/06/1969 (Box 2)
      - School Board Victory (Bishop), 06/09/1969 (Box 2)
    - July-December
      - Ann Arbor Arboretum, 07/06/1969 (Box 2)
      - Pig Eating in G.D. Rector Park, 07/12/1969 (Box 2)
        (Pergeaux, Eric)
      - VFW and GM Legion, 07/14/1969 (Box 2)
      - Tiol's (Wildcat Jackson), 07/16/1969 (Box 2)
      - General Store, 07/23/1969 (Box 2)
      - Detroit, 07/31/1969 (Box 2)
      - Hair, 9/69 (Box 2)
      - Bikes on Racks, 9/69 (Box 2)
        (Wexler)
      - Tall Ann Arbor Buildings at Night, 9/69 (Box 2)
      - People in Beds in Dungeon, West Quad, 09/03/1969 (Box 2)
      - Fleming at Hill for Freshmen, 09/03/1969 (Box 2)
        (Diehl)
      - Fleming at Hill for Freshmen, 09/03/1969 (Box 2)
      - Prick, 09/03/1969 (Box 2)
        (Argus)
      - Man on Street-Faces, 09/06/1969 (Box 2)
      - Daily Meeting on Prick Pic, 09/06/1969 (Box 2)
      - Michigan Union, 09/07/1969 (Box 2)
        (Edmonds)
      - Auction, 09/07/1969 (Box 2)
      - Tenants Union Meeting, 09/08/1969 (Box 2)
      - Marv. Esch Debates White Panthers, 09/08/1969 (Box 2)
      - Debate between Landsman and ? 9/69 (Box 2)
        (Pergeaux:)
      - Debate with Pigs in Dorm, 09/09/1969 (Box 2)
      - Landsman Debate, 09/09/1969 (Box 2)
      - Central Judie Typing Navy Recruiter, 09/17/1969 (Box 2)
      - ROTC is Smashed, 09/15/1969 (Box 2)
      - Rally for 1st Football Game Doc Losh, 09/19/1969 (Box 2)
      - Diag Rally, 09/19/1969 (Box 2)
      - Canterbury House Len Chandler, 09/19/1969 (Box 2)
      - Art Museum, 09/22/1969 (Box 2)
      - 1st (Protest?), 09/23/1969 (Box 2)
      - Plaza Rally with Fleming, 09/26/1969 (Box 2)
      - Al Capp, 09/28/1969 (Box 2)
      - Night Meeting, 09/29/1969 (Box 2)
      - Rugby Ad, 09/30/1969 (Box 2)
        (Judkis, Jim)
      - Fleming Tea, 09/30/1969 (Box 2)
        (Judkis)
      - New Mobe Meeting EMU, 10/04/1969 (Box 2)
      - SGC Bookstore, 10/08/1969 (Box 2)
        (Bassin, Donna)
      - CJS Hearing, 10/08/1969 (Box 2)
        (Bassin)
      - Black Law Students, 10/10/1969 (Box 2)